and lie about it to your wife!
(Girl:)Sorry for eavesdropping,
but did you know
(Girl:)they actually had
the song “Let It Go” in place
(Girl:)before they finalized the story?
(Raj:)Yeah, that's true. In fact,
they liked the song so much,
(Raj:)they retooled
the whole script around it.
(Girl:)Which is probably
why that movie sucks.
(Howard:)Here we are
talking about Frozen,
(Howard:)and yet, you got burned.
Miss, I'm so sorry.
(Raj:)How can you not like that movie?
(Girl:)I just think it gets more credit
than it deserves.
(Howard:)Oh, that's what I said
an hour ago.
(Girl:)Wow. You've been talking
about Frozen for an hour?
(Howard:)You should've seen us
after The Good Dinosaur.
(Raj:)It was a classic western
set in the post-Jurassic period,
(Raj:)and it changed my life.
(Sheldon:)Are you comfortable?
(Meemaw:)Very.
(Meemaw:)It's nice to rest
(Meemaw:)after 800 flights of stairs.
(Sheldon:)You were so cute,
huffin' and puffin'.
(knocking)